niagaracollege.ca 2019-12-17

# Niagara College Privacy Statement for Visitors to NiagaraCollege.ca

Niagara College is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors and to ensuring that you have a secure online experience. For most of our site, you are able to navigate through without providing any personal information. However, in some instances we may require some personal information in order to provide you with full services.

In these situations, the collection, use, disclosure, and retention of your personal information will be in compliance with **Ontario’s Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (FIPPA)** and with the **Niagara College Practice for the Freedom of Information and the Protection of Privacy**.

Additional Niagara College Practices can be found **here**.

* * *

### Student Privacy

Student privacy information can be found [here](https://www.niagaracollege.ca/privacy/student/).

* * *

### Use of Personal Information Collected Online

**The primary uses of personal information collected online are:**

  1. To help you quickly find services of information on the site.
  2. To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you.
  3. To alert you to special offers, updated information and other new services or programs

### Cookies

We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features, and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information that you’ve provided to them or that they’ve collected from your use of their services. You consent to our cookies if you continue to use our website.

Cookies are an industry standard and most major web sites use them. A cookie is a small text file that our site may place on your computer as a tool to remember your preferences. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. If you choose not to have your browser accept cookies from the site, you will still be able to view the text on the screens, however you may not experience a personalized visit and you may not be able to subscribe to the service offerings of the site.

A list of our cookies is [provided here](https://www.niagaracollege.ca/privacy/cookies/).

### Emailed and Mailed Marketing Materials

**At any time, you may choose to be removed from any of our mailing lists.** Please contact the Information Centre by email at [info@niagaracollege.ca](mailto:info@niagaracollege.ca), or by phone at 905-735-2211 extension 7559.

Email newsletters that you receive will have an “unsubscribe” link in the footer. The easiest way to directly unsubscribe from a specific communication is to click the “unsubscribe” link.

### Javascript

Many features of the Niagara College website use Javascript to function. We cannot guarantee the functionality of all website features if Javascript is disabled in your browser. If Javascript is disabled a warning will display at the top of each page.

### Website Errors and Display Issues

To report broken links or display errors please send an email to [webmaster@niagaracollege.ca](mailto:webmaster@niagaracollege.ca). Be sure to include the URL of the page that you were trying to visit, and the URL of the page which you clicked the broken link on (if available).
